Taylor, Mildred Frick; Papers apap280
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1921-1974; 1.8 cubic ft.
  - Joint Legislative Committee - Monetary Activities, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Laws of NY, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Legislative Payroll, 1959-1960; Undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - List of Chairman and Committee Members, Undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - List of Voters, 1943; Undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - List of Chairman and Committee Members, Undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Lyons Community Hospital, Undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Lyons Fire Department, Undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Medical Candidates - New Doctors, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Mildred Taylor - Heart Attack, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Monroe Apple, 1960; Undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Natural Resources Inventory - Lyons, NY, 1956 August 01 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - News Broadcast Speeches, 1960; Undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - News Clippings, 1947 November 18 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - News Clippings, 1948 July 22 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - News Clippings, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - News Clippings, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - News Clippings, Undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - News Clippings - Mildred Taylors Health/Announcement about End of Term as Wayne County Assembly Woman, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Newspapers, 1953; Undated (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - News Release - Registration for Station Wagons, 1960 February 05 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - News Release - Retirement, Undated (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Nominations for the Delegates and Alternates to the Republican State Convention, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - NYS Republican Platform - Rockefeller, 1970; Undated (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - NYS Thruway - Automobile Club of Syracuse Invitations, 1954 June; Undated (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - NYS Thruway - Campbell - Bennison vs. Governor's Thruway Plan, Undated (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - NYS Thruway - Correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - NYS Thruway - Expectations, 1949; Undated (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - NYS Thruway Fashions - Dey Brothers, 1954 June 24 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - NYS Thruway - Radio History, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - NYS Thruway - Souvenirs, 1954 June 24 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - NYS Thruway - Statement and Charts, Undated (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - NYS Thruway - Toll Schedules and Traffic Rules and Regulations, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Official Opening of the NYS Thruway - Program and Schedules, 1954 June 24 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Policy and Standards for Entrances to State Highways, Undated (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Preservation Materials, 1962; Undated (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Primary Campaign, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Primary Election Expenses, 1946; Undated (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Project Change - SUNY Cortland, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Public Officers Law, Undated (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Pultenville, Undated (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Radio News Broadcasts, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Reports of the 18th Annual Meeting and Convention of NYS of Young Republican Club, 1950 June 10 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Republican Recommendations, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Republican State Committee Appointments, 1944-1952 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Resolution: Continuing the Committee, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Robert A. Taft Reception Invitation, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Rochester Regional Hospital Council Meeting, 1966 January 31 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Roll of Delegates and Alternates to the Republican State Convention, 1946 September 3-4 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Rotary View - Wolcott Rotary Club, 1949 September 29 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Route 14, 1958-1959; Undated (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Rules and Regulations - Westchester Republican County Committee, 1954 May 25 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Rules of the Republican State Committee of NYS, 1944 April 11 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Sackets Harbor Summer Meeting, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - School Bus Transportation, 1961 May 12 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Senatorial District of the State of NY, Undated (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Sewerage Plans - Palmyra Village, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - "So you've been Elected Publicity Chairman!", Undated (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - State District of Finances, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Survey of Motels, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Tabor Registration, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Tabulation for Elections, 1943-1946 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Thank yous for Voting Mildred as Assembly Candidate, 1948-1956 (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - United States Military Academy, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Unofficial Poll on Judge Leadership, 1954 April 22 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Wayne County Bylaw Changes - Chairman Decisions, 1945-1947 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Wayne County Campaign - Dwight D. Eisenhower, 1952-1956; Undated (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Wayne County - Committee Members, 1943-1945; Undated (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Wayne County - Committee Meetings, 1944-1945; Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Wayne County - Committee Meetings, 1949 June (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Wayne County - Committee Meetings, 1949 September 29 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Wayne County - Committee Meetings, 1950 December 16 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Wayne County - Committee Meetings, 1951 September 08 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Wayne County - Committee Meetings, 1952 February 23 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Wayne County - Committee Meetings, 1952 June 21-23 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Wayne County - Committee Meetings, 1953 March 07 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Wayne County - Committee Meetings, 1953 June 06 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Wayne County - Committee Meetings, 1953 September 29 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Wayne County - Committee Meetings, 1954 June 30 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Wayne County - Committee Meetings, 1954 December 11 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Wayne County - Committee Meetings, 1955 June 29 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Wayne County - Committee Meetings, 1955 October 01 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Wayne County - Committee Meetings, 1956 March 31 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Wayne County - Committee Meetings (Taylor's Last Meeting as Chairman), 1956 December 29 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Wayne County - Correspondence, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Wayne County - Elmer G. Butts Candidacy, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Wayne County - Expenses, Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Wayne County - Go G.O.P.- Han John S. Fine, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Wayne County - Gubernatorial Vote, 1942; 1946; Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Wayne County - Hamlet of Marion- Route 21, 1958-1959 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Wayne County - Jesse C. Pettey, Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Wayne County - Members Special Statewide Committee For Dewey and Warren, 1948 October 18 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Wayne County - Petitions, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Wayne County - Phyllis A. Brasser Endorsement, 1944 December 13 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Wayne County - Press Releases, 1956; Undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Wayne County - Registration, Undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Wayne County - Republican Committee, 1921; 1945; Undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Wayne County - Route 14, 1956; 1959 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Wayne County - Sheriff Charles Wright's Retirement, 1945 April (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Wayne County - Vacancy for Surrogate and Children's Court Judge, 1954; Undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Wayne County - Watchers Certificate- Republican Party, Undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Wendell L. Willkie Nomination, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - What is $4.2 Billion Budget, 1961 June 02 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- New York State History, 1940-1970; 4.2 cubic ft.
  This series contains information on New York State History. As a member of the Standing Comittee on the affairs of villages and the Joint Committee on Historic Sites, Mildred worked to preserve various historical sites in New York State. Sites include the John Jay house, castles on Long Island, and churches. Taylor also worked to perserve the New York State Thruway since she saw it as an essential part of New York State's upcoming history. This collection also contains brochures on various museums, as well as meeting minutes from the Joint Legislative Committee, and correspondence with members from various historical societies. This collection also features documents that focus on the preservation of the Erie Canal (Barge Canal) and its surrounding areas that are essential to the history of New York State. Other prominent papers include walking tours of New York City and inspections of the value of various historical sites.
  - 175th Anniversary Battle of Long Island, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1000 Island Meeting, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The 1787 Bedford Court House; Its Significance in History and for the Future, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Abandoned Property - Charles A. Brind, 1954; 1959 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Agreement of Understanding Between the NYS Education Department and the NYS Historic Trust, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Albany Meeting, 1958-1960 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Alexander Hamilton House, 1960; Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - American Association for State and Local History - Annual Awards of Merit, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - American Association for State and Local History - Budget Summary, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Appointment Made by Governor Rockefeller, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Architecture Worth Saving in Wayne County, 1966-1967; Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Areas Administered by the National Park Service, 1955 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - The Art Gallery, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Atomic Authority Selects Area on Lake Ontario and St. Lawrence as Potential Sites for Demonstration Breeder Reactor, 1969 August 25 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Barge Canal, 1958; Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Barge Canal - Skenesborough Museum, Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Batavia - Thruway, Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Battle of Lake Erie Sesquicentennial - Souvenir Program, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Bedford Court House - Bedford Village - Westchester NY, 1968 June (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Bedford House - Exhibits, Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Biennial Report - Vermont Historic Sites Commission, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Black River Locks, 1958-1960 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Blue BVS Lines, Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Boscobel - A Progress Report, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Boscobel Restoration, Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Boughton Hill Site as a National Historic Landmark, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Broome County Historical Society, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - The Brush House, 1967 November 21 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Budget, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Burning Spring - Town of Bristol - Ontario County, 1967 October 17 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Canal Cruise, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Canal Museum - Moss Island Site, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Canal Society of NYS (1 of 3), 1956-1957; Undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Canal Society of NYS (2 of 3), 1956-1957; Undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Canal Society of NYS (3 of 3), 1956-1957; Undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Capital City News Bureau, 1958; Undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Capital Projects Budget Priority Plans, 1960-1970 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Carleton Island (Fort Haldim), 1968 January (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Castle MacFergus, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Catalog of Charts of the Great Lakes and Connecting Waters, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Chapellier Studios, Undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Chemung County Historical Society, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Chesapeake and Ohio Canal, Undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Clinton House, 1957-1960 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Clinton House - Guy Manor Park, 1957; 1959-1960; Undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Cobblestone Society, Undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Commission to Commemorate the War of 1812 and the Star Spangled Banner, 1958; 1964-1965; Undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - A Compilation of Reports on Washington's Headquarters - Hasbrouck House, Newburg and Orange County, June 1970 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Conrad L. Wirth - Talk on Natural and Human History, 1970 June 10 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Consensus List: NYS Historic Sites of Primary Importance Not Already Listed on the National Register of Historic Sites and Buildings, Undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Consolidation and Education Law, Undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Constable Hall - St. Lawrence Seaway, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - The Construction and Enlargement of the Erie Canal - An Incident of Lafayette's Tour approximately 1878, Undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Cooperstown, 1960; 1962; Undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Cooperstown Meeting, 1960 August (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Copake Iron Works, 1968 May (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Cords Castle - MacFergus, 1945; 1957 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence - Attorney General Javits, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence - Booth, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence with Conrad L. Wirth about the Preservation of the National Park Service, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence Historical, 1951-1952; 1954 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Correspondence - Historical, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence - Historical (1 of 2), 1958-1960 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence - Historical (2 of 2), 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Correspondence - Historical, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence - Historical, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Correspondence - Historical, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Correspondence - Historical, Undated (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Correspondence - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Correspondence - "Preservation and Restoration of Historic Sites", 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Costs - Erie Canal, Ft. Hunter NY, 1957; 1959 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - County Historian, 1958 March (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - County Historian, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Criteria for Evaluating Historic Sites and Buildings, Undated (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Crown Point - Champlain Festival, 1957-1959 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Danascar Estate, 1957 August 16 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Daniel Gomez, A Pioneer Merchant of Early NY, 1951 December (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Daughters of the American Revolution - Hoosac Wallomoac Chapter, 1958-1959; Undated (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Dey Mansion - Washington Headquarters, Undated (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Downtown Museum of the City of NY, 1968 February (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Duke Oaths Summer Theatre, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Dutch Settlers Society of Albany - Fort Aiden, Undated (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Education Low - NYS History Publications Corporation, 1967 December 19-20 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Erie Canal - Bottoming Out (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Erie Canal - Fort Hunter, 1956-1958; Undated (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Erie Canal - Little Falls, 1957-1959 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Erie Canal Museum - Dewitt Bullock, Undated (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Erie Canal - News, 1957; Undated (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Erie Canal - Restoration, 1956-1958; Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Erie Canal - Venera Cruise, 1957-1960; Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Erie Canal - Weighlock Building, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Evaluation of Old Delaware Academy Building - Delhi, NY, 1967 June (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Existing Conditions - Herkimer House, 1970 April 23 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Existing Conditions Report on the Washington; Headquarters (Hasbrouck House), Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Fairfield Academy and Fairfield Medical College, Fairfield Herkimer County, 1967 October 13 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Fairfield Academy - Fairfield Herkimer County, 1968 January (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Fenton Mansion, 1968 January 13 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - First Golf Course, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - "Flesh on the Bones of History" - Archeology at the Schuyler Mansion, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Fort Delaware, 1958; Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Fort Hunter - Governor Rockefellers Visit, 1957-1960; Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Fort Hunter - Pictures, Undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Fort Niagara, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Fort Ticonderoga - Historic Crown Point, 1942; 1958; Undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Fort Ticonderoga - Montcalm Commemoration, 1958 July 12-13 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Fort Totten - Flushing, NY, Undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Four Mile - Creek Park Project, Undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Gannagaro Association, 1968; Undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Garibaldi and Meucci Memorial Museum, 1968 November (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - General Directors Report, 1970 June 10 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Geneva Historical Society and Museum Address, 1962 November 11 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Glenn H. Curtis's Memorial, 1956-1957; Undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Gomez House, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Guide Posts for a History Collection, 1962 June (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - A Guide to Historic Buffalo, Undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Guide to Washington D.C, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Guidelines for Establishment of Historic Preservation Fund, 1969 August (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Hamilton House, 1957; 1959-1960; Undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Herkimer House, 1970 April (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Historic Canal Sites Committee Meeting, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Historic Landmark Journeys in NYS, Undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Historic Marker Program (1 of 2), 1957; 1959; Undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Historic Marker Program (2 of 2), 1957; 1959; Undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Historic Marker Program - Suggestions, 1957; Undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Historic Old Fort Niagara, Undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Historic Painted Post, NY - Indian Monument, 1950; 1957 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Historic Significance of the Fort Hunter Area, 1967 August (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Historic Site - Inspection Trips, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Historic Sites, 1968 January 15 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Historic Sites Commission - Report for Biennium, 1950 June 30 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Historic Sites of NYS, Undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Historic Sites Personnel, Undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Historic Sites Resolution, 1957; 1961 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Historical Analysis of the Nicholas Herkimer Farm, 1970 April 23 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Historical Societies of NYS, 1957; 1959 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Historical Societies of NYS, 1960 May 10 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Historical Societies of NYS, 1963 January 15 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Historical Trust Capital Budget, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Historical Trust Legislative Program, 1969 November 17 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - History News - American Association for State and Local History, 1962 June (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - History of the Newark State School, Undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Holland Land Office, Undated (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - House Applications Subcommittee for Interior and Related Agencies, Undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - HUD Grant Aids Restoration of 19th Century Theater, 1969 August 23-24 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Hudson - Champlain Festival, Undated (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Hudson River Lighthouses, 1967 November 8 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Hunt House - Mt. Vernon, NY, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Hyde Hall, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Hyde Hall - Cooperstown Otsego County, 1968 January (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Innerwick - Flushing, NY, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Inspection Tours of Historic Sites, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Inspector II - Champlain Canal and Lake Tour, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Internal Improvement - Utica Patriot, Undated (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Irondequoit Chapter House, 1957; Undated (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Jackson and Perkins Rose Gardens, 1969 September (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Jasper County Pioneer Historical Society, Undated (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Jefferson County Historical Museum, Undated (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - John Brown's Farm, 1953; 1957 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - John Jay House, 1953; 1957-1959; Undated (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - John Jay Property, 1957 September 10 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Joint Legislative Committee Meeting, 1957 August (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Joint Legislative Committee Meeting, 1958 January (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Joint Legislative Committee Meeting, 1958 December 9 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Joint Legislative Committee Meeting, 1959 February (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Joint Legislative Committee Meeting, 1960 March 14 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Joint Legislative Committee Meeting, 1960 September (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Joint Legislative Committee Meeting, 1960 October (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Joint Legislative Committee on Preservation and Restoration of Historic Societies, 1957-1958 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Joint Legislative Committee on Preservation and Restoration of Historic Societies, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Joint Legislative Committee on Preservation and Restoration of Historic Sites - Payroll and Monetary Requests, 1957-1960; Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Joint Legislative Committee on Preservation and Restoration of Historic Sites - Remarks at Informal Luncheon Meeting, 1958 February 1 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Joint Legislative Committee Organization, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Joint Legislative Committee Organization Follow Up, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Joshua Smith House, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Kent Delord House, 1958; Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Kings Landing, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Knickerbocker Historical Society, 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Laws of New York, Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Lincklaen House, Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Lithuanian Nobleman First Latin Schoolmaster of NY, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Lloyd Manor House, 1967 November 20 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - L.M. Hoyt Estate, 1969 October (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Local History Conferences, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Log Cabin Days - Ohio Historical Society, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Lower Lock Farm, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Lyndhurst, Undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Macdonough Memorial - Plattsburg, Clinton County, 1968 January (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Madison Barracks, 1967 November 6 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Map of Connecticut - Historic Sites, 1962; Undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Map of County of the Five Nations of the Iroquois Indians, Undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Map of Ontario County, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Marvin A. Rapp, 1957-1958; Undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Master Plan for Johnson Hall, 1970 September (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Meeting of Board Directions, 1962 May (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Meeting - Clifton Springs Sanitarium Company, 1969 December 16 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Meeting of Historic Council, 1959 February 2 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Memorandum of Understanding Between The State Council of Parks and Outdoor Recreation and the New York State Historical Trust and the Hudson River Valley Commission, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Memorandum on Historic Preservation, Undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Memorial Plagues, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Memorial Services - Veterans of National Guard and Naval Militia - Monument, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Mildred Taylor - Travel Expenses, 1959; Undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Millard Fillmore Birthplace - Cayuga County, 1968 June (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Modes of Travel and Transport, 1953 August 11 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Mohawk Valley Towns Association, Undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Moss Island - Little Falls, NY, 1967 November 28 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Mount Defiance, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Mount Vernon - St. Paul's Church, 1940; 1958; 1960; Undated (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Musical Artists, 1962-1963; Undated (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Mystic Seaport, Undated (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - National Order of Women Legislators, 1955-1956; 1963; 1965-1966; Undated (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Natural Heritage Trust Law, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - The Needs of Opportunities for Historic Preservation in NYS, Undated (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - New York City's Multimillion Dollar, "Village Green", Undated (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - New York - Folklore Quarterly, Undated (Box 3, Folder 49)